Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11 Locals, 2.
  - Local 1105
    - Local 1105 John Jurka Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Jurka to R.E. Powers Regarding Negotiations and Organization with December 4, 1938, Letter to Matles, December 3, 1938; 16.
      - Jurka to Matles Regarding Organization, January 31, 1939; 17.
    - Local 1105 John Jurka Outgoing Correspondence, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - John Jurka to James Matles Regarding Organization at St. Louis Westinghouse, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and Unemployment, February 8, 1939; 1.
      - Jurka to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Organization, March 7, 1939; 2.
      - Jurka to Matles Regarding Seniority, Incentive, and Organization, June 5, 1939; 3.
      - Jurka to Matles Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, July 10, 1939; 4.
      - Jurka to J.C. Almeida Regarding Organization and IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, October 10, 1939; 5.
      - Jurka to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, September 6, 1939; 6.
    - Local 1105 General Incoming Correspondence, 1934-1951 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Julius Emspak to John Colley Regarding Transfers, November 2, 1934; 1.
      - Emspak to Colley Regarding Transfers, November 20, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to Colley Regarding Transfer, December 2, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Local 1105 Regarding Dues, October 4, 1939; 4.
      - Emspak to Thomas Rice, September 24, 1940; 5.
      - Emspak to C.A. Stephenson Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 25, 1940; 6.
      - Emspak to Rice Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 16, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to George Krug Regarding Per Capita, June 14, 1946; 8.
      - Emspak to Rice Regarding Per Capita, January 21, 1947; 9.
      - Emspak to Rice Regarding Per Capita, February 17, 1947; 10.
      - Emspak to Rice Regarding Per Capita, November 14, 1947; 11.
      - Emspak to Local 1105 Regarding Red-baiting, May 14, 1951; 12.
      - James Matles to Local 1105 Regarding Negotiations, November 30, 1940; 13.
      - Matles to Frank Petrolowitz Regarding Negotiations, March 27, 1941; 14.
      - Matles to Carl Leaveh Regarding Negotiations, April 16, 1941; 15.
      - Matles to Frank Petrolowitz Regarding Negotiations, April 26, 1941; 16.
      - Matles to Carl Leaven Regarding Staff Members, May 14, 1941; 17.
      - Matles to Leaven Regarding Wages, November 12, 1941; 18.
    - Local 1105 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1952 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Simpson Berry to UE Regarding Westinghouse Conference, May 20, 1940; 1.
      - Berry to James Matles Regarding Organization and District Boundaries, December 6, 1940; 2.
      - Barry to Matles Regarding Strikes and Wages, December 6, 1940; 3.
      - Dorothy Brunet to Julius Emspak Regarding National Strike Fund, November 26, 1952; 4.
      - John Colley to the Congress of Industrial Organizations Regarding Transfer, October 19, 1937; 5.
      - Colley to Emspak Regarding Transfer, November 24, 1937; 6.
      - George Krug to Emspak Regarding Strikes, March 15, 1946; 7.
      - Krug to UE Regarding Per Capita, June 11, 1946; 8.
      - Francis LaBonte to UE Regarding Negotiations, Wages, and Women, June 7, 1942; 9.
      - Carl Leaven to Matles Regarding Contract, April 27, 1941; 10.
      - Leaven to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 11, 1941; 11.
      - Leaven to Matles Regarding Westinghouse Conference Board, October 20, 1941; 12.
      - Leaven to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Wages, November 6, 1941; 13.
      - Leaven to UE Regarding Officers, April 11, 1942; 14.
      - Frank Petrolowitz to Matles Regarding Contract, April 25, 1940; 15.
      - Thomas Rice to UE Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 12, 1945; 16.
      - Rice to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 7, 1947; 17.
      - Rice to UE Regarding Packinghouse Workers Strike, March 7, 1949; 18.
      - Emmett Ruckman to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 31, 1939; 19.
      - Sam Skinner to UE Regarding African-Americans, April 27, 1943; 20.
    - Local 1105 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1945-1951 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - C.A. Stephenson to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 1945; 1.
      - Hubert Thomson to Fred Hartley Regarding Red-baiting and Evansville, October 4, 1948; 2.
      - Thomson to Charles Keisten Regarding Red-baiting and Evansville, October 4, 1948; 3.
      - Thomson to Gerald Landis Regarding Red-baiting and Evansville, October 4, 1948; 4.
      - Thomson to Harry Truman Regarding Red-baiting and Evansville, October 4, 1948; 5.
      - Thomson to Albert Eberhad Regarding Local 813, October 4, 1948; 6.
      - Thomson to Emspak Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, May 2, 1951; 7.
    - Local 1105 Chicago, Illinois Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Local 1105 Constitution Correspondence, 1945-1982 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Local 1105 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, November 1937-June 1940 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Local 1105 Report of Financial Secretary, April 1937-March 1938 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Local 1105 Per Capita, April 1938-April 1940 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Local 1105 Per Capita, May-July 1940 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Local 1105 Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Buck to James Carey Regarding Westinghouse Conference, March 11, 1937; 1.
      - John Jurka to John Colley Regarding Transfers, September 30, 1937; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Al Stonkus Regarding Suspensions, June 24, 1939; 3.
      - Stonkus to James Matles Regarding Negotiations and Organization with August 14, 1939, R.E. Powers Letters to Local 1105, August 1939; 4.
      - Matles to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Finances, May 7, 1943; 5.
      - Alice Smith to Matles Regarding Guards Organization, October 5, 1949; 6.
    - Local 1105 Miscellaneous, 1955-1981 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Local 1105 Strikes, Subsidies, and Other Monies, 1952-1977 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Local 1105 Supplements, 1958-1981 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Local 1105 Supplements and Agreements, 1940-1963 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Local 1105 Supplemental Material, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Local 1105 Supplement Negotiations, 1940-1962 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Local 1105 Chicago Westinghouse Strike Funds and Correspondence, 1958-1985 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Local 1105 Job Descriptions, undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Local 1105 Contracts, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Local 1107
    - Local 1107 Officers Lists, January 8, 1947-January 30, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Local 1107 Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Rose Dale Regarding Dues and Veterans, October 26, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Local 1107 Outgoing Correspondence, 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Rose Dale to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Officers with Dues List, January 8, 1947; 1.
      - Dale to Emspak Regarding Local Structure, February 22, 1947; 2.
      - Dale to UE Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, November 16, 1950; 3.
    - Local 1107 Local Structure, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, January 16, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, February 7, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, February 26, 1947; 3.
      - Secretary of Emspak to DeMaio, March 11, 1947; 4.
    - Local 1107 Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Organization, June 4, 1945; 1.
      - Lou Majors to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 30, 1946; 2.
  - Local 1109
    - Local 1109 Officers Lists, September 1938-March 21, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Local 1109 Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1952 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - James Carey to George Hayden Regarding Strikes, October 1938; 1.
      - Carey to Edward Kukla Regarding Strikes, October 18, 1938; 2.
      - Carey to Hayden Regarding Zanesville Live Material Organization, December 29, 1938; 3.
      - Carey to Hayden Regarding Factionalism, September 29, 1939; 4.
      - Ernest DeMaio to Esther Milulshi Regarding Military Contracts, March 21, 1942; 5.
      - Julius Emspak to Frank Skubitz Regarding Organization, March 23, 1937; 6.
      - Emspak to Theo Kerwin Regarding Negotiations, April 8, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak to Charles Szatkowski Regarding Organization, May 8, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak to Szatkowski Regarding Organization, June 11, 1937; 9.
      - Emspak to Szatkowski Regarding Contracts and Seniority, July 14, 1937; 10.
      - Emspak to Szatkowski Regarding Finances, August 20, 1937; 11.
      - Emspak to Szatkowski Regarding Finances, September 17, 1937; 12.
      - Emspak to Joseph Koban Regarding Finances, Unemployment, and Negotiations, November 2, 1937; 13.
      - Emspak to Koban Regarding Per Capita, January 5, 1938; 14.
      - Emspak to F. Olszewski Regarding Per Capita, March 31, 1938; 15.
      - Emspak to Ted Kerwin Regarding Unemployment, December 21, 1938; 16.
      - Emspak to Hayden Regarding Staff Members, May 9, 1940; 17.
      - Emspak to Esther Mikulski Regarding UE News, June 13, 1940; 18.
      - Emspak to Hayden Regarding Contracts, April 18, 1941; 19.
      - Emspak to Edward Loewe Regarding Dues and Veterans, September 19, 1945; 20.
      - James Matles to Skubitz Regarding Oneida Line Material Organization, November 23, 1937; 21.
      - Matles to Eugene Olszewski Regarding Musicians Organization, March 25, 1938; 22.
      - Matles to Olszewski Regarding Organization, May 13, 1938; 23.
      - Matles to Kukla Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization and Westinghouse Runaway Shops, January 4, 1939; 24.
      - Matles to Kukla Regarding Zanesville and Stroudsburg Line Material Organization, January 12, 1939; 25.
      - Matles to Kukla Regarding Staff Members, January 13, 1939; 26.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, January 30, 1939; 27.
      - Matles to Kukla Regarding Stroudsburg Line Material Organization, January 31, 1939; 28.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, July 6, 1939; 29.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, November 30, 1939; 30.
      - Matles to Earl McGrew Regarding Line Material Organization, March 25, 1940; 31.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Stroudsburg Line Material Organization, May 2, 1940; 32.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Line Material Organization, May 28, 1940; 33.
      - Matles to Mikulski Regarding Contracts, September 18, 1940; 34.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Line Material Organization, October 23, 1941; 35.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, November 25, 1941; 36.
      - Matles to Hayden Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, December 5, 1941; 37.
      - Matles to Mikulski Regarding Overtime, February 17, 1942; 38.
      - Matles to Joseph Pisarkek Regarding Contracts, February 26, 1952; 39.
      - Executive Secretary to Szatkowski Regarding Organization, April 23, 1937; 40.
    - Local 1109 Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1952 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - George Hayden to James Carey Regarding Strikes, September 29, 1938; 1.
      - Hayden to Carey Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, December 21, 1938; 2.
      - Hayden to Carey Regarding Factionalism and Negotiations, September 25, 1939; 3.
      - Hayden to James Matles Regarding Stroudsburg Line Material Organization, May 21, 1940; 4.
      - Theodore Kerwin to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 1938; 5.
      - Kerwin to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 16, 1938; 6.
      - Kerwin to Emspak Regarding 1946 UE Convention and Factionalism, September 1946; 7.
      - Joseph Kuban to Emspak Regarding Negotiations and Unemployment, October 21, 1937; 8.
      - Kuban to UE Regarding Per Capita, December 30, 1937; 9.
      - Edward Kukla to Emspak Regarding Expulsions, September 26, 1938; 10.
      - Kukla to Carey Regarding Strikes, October 15, 1938; 11.
      - Kukla to Matles Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, January 16, 1939; 12.
      - Kukla to Matles Regarding Wages and Zanesville Line Material Organization, February 12, 1939; 13.
      - Kukla to Matles Regarding Wages and Zanesville Line Material Organization, February 22, 1939; 14.
      - Kukla to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 7, 1940; 15.
      - Edward Loewe to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, September 15, 1945; 16.
      - Loewe to Emspak Regarding Charter with Charter, April 28, 1952; 17.
      - Earl McGrew to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Grievances, Company Get Together, Companion Union, and Line Material Organization, March 22, 1940; 18.
      - McGrew to Emspak Regarding General Television and NLRB, March 24, 1940; 19.
      - Esther Mikulski to Emspak Regarding Officers, June 11, 1940; 20.
      - Mikulski to A. Towson Regarding Wages and Factionalism, August 14, 1940; 21.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Contracts and Unemployment, September 17, 1940; 22.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Conscription, October 21, 1940; 23.
      - Mikulski to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 16, 1941; 24.
      - Mikulski to Emspak Regarding Negotiations and Contracts, March 31, 1941; 25.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Stroudsburg Line Material Organization, September 21, 1941; 26.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, December 7, 1941; 27.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Line Material and Contracts, February 12, 1942; 28.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization, February 16, 1942; 29.
      - Mikulski to Matles Regarding Zanesville Line Material Organization and Unemployment, March 7, 1942; 30.
      - Eugene Olszewski to Matles Regarding Musicians Organization, March 23, 1938; 31.
      - Olszewski to Emspak Regarding Negotiations and Line Material Plants Organization, May 6, 1938; 32.
      - Frank Skubitz to Emspak Regarding Organization, March 25, 1937; 33.
      - Skubitz to UE Regarding Organization, April 1937; 34.
      - Charles Szatkowski to Carey Regarding Organization, April 21, 1937; 35.
      - Szatkowski to Stella Abrams Regarding Officers, May 8, 1937; 36.
      - Szatkowski to Emspak Regarding Local Picnic and Questionnaire, June 29, 1937; 37.
      - Szatkowski to Emspak Regarding Milwaukee Congress of Industrial Organizations, July 5, 1937; 38.
      - Szatkowski to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 1937; 39.
    - Local 1109 South Milwaukee Correspondence, 1957-1973 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Local 1109 Notices of Delinquency/Suspension, November 1937-June 1940 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Local 1109 Report of Financial Secretary, July 1937-February 1939 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Local 1109 Per Capita Reports, July 1938-July 1940 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Local 1109 Newspaper Clipping, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Local 1109 Organization, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Meyer Adelman to Julius Emspak, March 15, 1937; 1.
      - Emspak to Adelman, March 23, 1937; 2.
      - Emspak to Adelman, March 26, 1937; 3.
      - Adelman to Emspak, April 2, 1937; 4.
    - Local 1109 Skobitz Firing, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Lloyd Andrews to UE, December 23, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Gardner, December 31, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak to Andrews, December 31, 1940; 3.
      - Gardner to Emspak, January 16, 1941; 4.
      - Gardner to Andrews, January 16, 1941; 5.
    - Local 1109 Strike, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - Phil Smith to James Matles, November 26, 1945; 1.
      - Matles to Smith, December 3, 1945; 2.
      - Smith to the National Labor Relations Board, April 15, 1946; 3.
    - Local 1109 Memoranda and Correspondence, 1938-1952 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Average Hourly Rates, December 1938; 1.
      - Fred Gardner to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, December 26, 1940; 2.
      - Memo Regarding War Labor Board, March 27, 1944; 3.
      - John Shaffer to James Matles Regarding Contracts, February 23, 1952; 4.
    - Local 1109 710 Forms, 1947-1973 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Local 1110
    - Local 1110 Constitution, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Local 1110 Contract, May 1939 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Local 1110 Officers Lists, October 27, 1938-November 10, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Local 1110 Officers Resolution, Chicago Sub-District and Factionalism, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Local 1110 Membership, Resolution Regarding Coil Industry Organization, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Local 1110 Rose Hudec Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - James Carey to Rose Hudec Regarding District 11 and Factionalism, February 25, 1939; 1.
      - Carey to Hudec Regarding Mt. Carmel Visit, June 16, 1939; 2.
      - Carey to Hudec Regarding District 11 and Factionalism, November 9, 1939; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Hudec Regarding Finances, Contracts, and Organization, April 19, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Organization, April 26, 1937; 5.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Finances, May 6, 1937; 6.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Finances and Staff Members, June 22, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Per Capita and Congress of Industrial Organizations, July 29, 1937; 8.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Per Capita, August 4, 1937; 9.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Per Capita, August 20, 1937; 10.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding District 11 and Factionalism, November 20, 1937; 11.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Per Capita, November 24, 1937; 12.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Utilities Organization, December 2, 1937; 13.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Seniority, December 23, 1937; 14.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Contract, April 25, 1938; 15.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Radio Conference and Building Trades Organization, May 23, 1938; 16.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Philco Boycotts, June 23, 1938; 17.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Sickle Coil Organization, June 29, 1938; 18.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Strike Defender Ford and Boycotts, August 3, 1938; 19.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Unemployment and Dues, October 24, 1938; 20.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Unemployment and Dues, November 23, 1938; 21.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding UE News, February 17, 1939; 22.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Maytag Strike, Political Action, Factionalism, and District 11, February 27, 1939; 23.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Radio Conference and Open Shop Drive, March 20, 1939; 24.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Contracts, May 24, 1939; 25.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Carey Visit, June 7, 1939; 26.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Factionalism, July 25, 1939; 27.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Unemployment, August 14, 1939; 28.
      - Emspak to Hudec Regarding Meissner Los Angeles Organization, August 25, 1939; 29.
      - James Matles to Hudec Regarding Philco Contracts, March 28, 1939; 30.
      - Matles to Hudec Regarding Films, August 25, 1939; 31.
      - Matles to Hudec Regarding Contracts, June 3, 1938; 32.
      - Matles to Hudec Regarding Sickle Coil Organization, July 20, 1939; 33.
      - Matles to Hudec Regarding Sickle Coil Organization, August 1, 1939; 34.
      - Matles to Hudec Regarding Emspak Visit, November 14, 1939; 35.
      - Matles to Hudec Regarding Emspak Visit, November 15, 1939; 36.
    - Local 1110 Rose Hudec Outgoing Correspondence, 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Rose Hudec to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, Staff Members, and Officers, April 22, 1937; 1.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, April 25, 1937; 2.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, April 29, 1937; 3.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Dues Check-off, May 9, 1937; 4.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Dues, May 11, 1937; 5.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Officers and Insurance, May 12, 1937; 6.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Address Change, June 18, 1937; 7.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 12, 1937; 8.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Staff Members, July 12, 1937; 9.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 19, 1937; 10.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 31, 1937; 11.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 16, 1937; 12.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 19, 1937; 13.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding UE Officers, September 18, 1937; 14.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Officers, and UE Constitution, November 12, 1937; 15.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and District 11, November 15, 1937; 16.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and District 11, November 23, 1937; 17.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Negotiations and Firings, December 3, 1937; 18.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and District 11, December 7, 1937; 19.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Local Newspaper, Per Capita, and Seniority, December 17, 1937; 20.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 17, 1937; 21.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 19, 1938; 22.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Officers and Political Action, March 21, 1938; 23.
    - Local 1110 Rose Hudec Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Rose Hudec to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Sickle Coil Organization, May 19, 1938; 1.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Radio Conference, May 31, 1938; 2.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Philco Boycotts, June 16, 1938; 3.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Sickle Coil Organization, June 20, 1938; 4.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding 1938 UE Convention, July 18, 1938; 5.
      - Hudec to All UE Locals Regarding District 11, July 25, 1938; 6.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Philco Boycotts and Strike Fund, August 1, 1938; 7.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, August 9, 1938; 8.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Address Change, August 17, 1938; 9.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, August 18, 1938; 10.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Contracts, April 19, 1938; 11.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Princeton Congress of Industrial Organizations, October 18, 1938; 12.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Finances and Unemployment, November 17, 1938; 13.
      - Hudec to James Carey Regarding Political Action, February 12, 1939; 14.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Radio Conference, Factionalism, and District 11, February 18, 1939; 15.
      - Hudec to Carey Regarding Factionalism and District 11 with District Constitution Excerpt and District Council Program, February 20, 1939; 16.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and District 11, February 21, 1939; 17.
    - Local 1110 Rose Hudec Outgoing Correspondence, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Rose Hudec to Julius Emspak Regarding Negotiations, March 17, 1939; 1.
      - Hudec to James Carey Regarding District Council Meeting and Local 1113, March 9, 1939; 2.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Contracts, May 19, 1939; 3.
      - Hudec to Carey Regarding Carey Visit and Indiana Congress of Industrial Organizations, June 13, 1939; 4.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Factionalism, and Wages with Wage Rates, July 19, 1939; 5.
      - Hudec to James Matles Regarding 1939 UE Convention and Per Capita, July 27, 1939; 6.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding 1939 UE Convention and Unemployment, August 8, 1939; 7.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Finances and Films, August 17, 1939; 8.
      - Hudec to Carey Regarding Factionalism and Officers, October 18, 1939; 9.
      - Hudec to Emspak Regarding Factionalism with October 16, 1939, Charles Rutson Letter to Local 1110 and Anonymous Letters, October 18, 1939; 10.
      - Hudec to Matles Regarding Factionalism and District 11, October 20, 1939; 11.